http://www.dearcupid.org/pages/privacy-policy.html

New here? Register in under one minute
Already a member? Login242919 questions, 1077091 answers
DearCupid.ORG relationship advice
Got a relationship, dating, love or sex question? Ask for help!Search
New Questions Answers . Most Discussed Viewed . Unanswered . Followups . Forums . Top agony aunts . About Us .  Articles  . Sitemap
DearCupid.org privacy policy
Your privacy is important to us.
Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use , and how we safeguard your information.
We never sell your personal information to third parties.
Log Files
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.
The information in the log files include
your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
Cookies and Web Beacons
We do use cookies to help us manage your account if you create an account and login.
If you don't want these, don't create an account.
We also use third party advertisements to support our hosting costs.
Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.
This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
DoubleClick DART cookies
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).
This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).
The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).
DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.
It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.
You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx
You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.
However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.
This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.
Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
Asking questions / giving answers
Your questions and answers will be published publically but if you choose to write anonymously, we will not show your username or other details
(unless we screw up and make a mistake, but we'll try not to do that).
Please use common sense and don't use people's real names or anything that could
identify you if you don't want to be identified.
If you think someone you write on here anonymously revealing your identity will be truly awful, we'd recommend
you don't write in.
Other issues
The biggest chance of someone breaching your privacy is on your computer. If you visit and then someone sees your history of websites visited
they may see what questions you viewed or asked. Most modern browsers allow you to browse "InPrivate" or anonymously so you should look into that
or make sure you delete cookies and browser history if you share your computer.
All Content Copyright (C) DearCupid.ORG 2004-2008 - we actively monitor for copyright theft
0!
